{
  "extraDescription": "NB: operands are never negative",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-10"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 10",
      "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 10",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 11",
      "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 10",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &minus; 1",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 11",
      "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 7",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 10",
      "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; 11",
      "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &minus; 4",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "1"
    }
  ]
}
